(Sheldon:)- Show me...
- Sheldon?
[SPEAKING IN MANDARIN]
(Leonard:)I'm sorry.
Look, do you have a second?
(Sheldon:)A second what? Pair of underwear?
(Penny:)I was just wondering
if I could talk to you.
(Penny:)It's about Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Why me?
Why not Koothrappali or Wolowitz?
(Penny:)Well, Raj can't talk to me
unless he's drunk.
(Penny:)And Wolowitz is, you know, disgusting.
SHELDON:
Yes, I suppose he is.
(Penny:)All I'm saying
is you know Leonard the best.
(Sheldon:)Not necessarily. I'm often surprised
by my lack of familiarity with Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Just the other day, I discovered
he not only has a loofah, he hides it.
(Sheldon:)Why do you suppose a man
would be ashamed of having a loofah?
(Sheldon:)I myself prefer to have my excess
epithelial cells slough off naturally...
(Sheldon:)...but I don't condemn those
who seek to accelerate the process.
(Sheldon:)And until recently, I had no idea
that despite his lactose intolerance...
(Sheldon:)...he can tolerate small amounts
of nonfat ice cream...
(Sheldon:)...without producing a noxious gas...